ELIZABETH BOSS

6602 NE Tillamook Street, Portland, Oregon 97213 503.419.8659 • lizzie.boss@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I have over seven years of progressive experience in legal positions, with solid and current general office skills. I consistently have a genuinely cheerful and positive attitude; I am a self-starter and a team player. I work well under pressure, maintaining a calm and professional demeanor.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bodyfelt Mount LLP • Portland, Oregon • March — June 2013 Legal Assistant, Civil Trial Litigation

Worked in a deadline-driven law practice, supporting two attorneys; drafted correspondence to clients, opposing counsel, various courts, and judges; determined and followed pertinent case status and court deadlines; drafted various legal pleadings and documents for submission to opposing parties and court(s); researched cases cited within pleadings; populated and maintained calendars and schedules for multiple people; created, formatted, and maintained firm's website.

Tonkon Torp LLP • Portland, Oregon • June 2007 — August 2012 Legal Assistant, Corporate Immigration, including paralegal responsibilities

Worked in an extremely fast-passed practice group, supporting up to four attorneys and six paralegals; drafted attorney letters, including letters to the U.S. Customs and Immigration Service (USCIS); drafted immigration forms with INSZoom software (Adjustment of Status Applications, One-Step Applications; individual I-131, I-765, H-1B, H-4, H-3 Trainees, etc.); compiled up to ten daily complex petitions and various applications; billed own hours on Elite software; edited attorneys' and other paralegals' time entries in Elite software; contacted USCIS regarding various client issues; maintained calendars of multiple attorneys and paralegals; proofread, corrected, and finalized attorney letters and other correspondence; maintained daily mail log; met with clients for initial consultations and case status review; drafted fee agreements; closed files, and drafted closing letters to client; corresponded with clients' prior counsel; researched updated and changing laws; scheduled seminars including CLEs; attended ongoing computer program training inside and outside the firm; corresponded with clients via email and phone regarding case status; drafted and finalized client billing, sent out, and followed-up on outstanding balances; continually uploaded client information into various client websites (INSZoom, Elite, Desksite, and Outlook); trained six new employees to the practice group.

Dolan Griggs LLP • Portland, Oregon • August 2006 — May 2007 Legal Assistant

Drafted legal documents: Pleadings, Certificates of Service, Contingency Fee Agreements, Hourly Agreements; drafted letters to clients, opposing attorneys; performed electronic filing; filed documents in federal and state courts; notarized documents; researched opposing parties on internet; opened, made decisions, and distributed mail; calendared pertinent deadlines in Outlook and ProLaw: trial dates, depositions, etc.; scheduled court reporters; scheduled depositions; exhibit stamped; Bates stamped; turned single files into litigation files; input client information to server; scheduled new client consultations; sent out client copies; created and maintained discovery binders; ordered BOLI files; created, maintained, and distributed daily and weekly event reports to each attorney; input law clerks' hours daily; proofread and corrected attorneys' letters; closed files, and drafted closing letters to client; corresponded with opposing attorneys and legal assistants of case status, etc., scanned mail, Pleadings, etc. into server; answered multi-line phone and screened calls to attorneys; ordered office supplies.

OTHER JOBS HELD

- Administrative Assistant, American Benefits Insurance, Portland, Oregon (March August 2006)
- Server, Dessert Noir, Beaverton, Oregon (November 2005 February 2006)
- Sales Associate, Ann Taylor Loft, Portland, Oregon (August December 2005)
- Model, Ryan Artists, Portland, Oregon (1997 2008)
- Data Entry, Ryan Artists, Portland, Oregon (April June 2005)
- Showroom Host/Receptionist, Kuni BMW, Cadillac, Saab LLC (December 2003 March 2005)

SKILLS, LICENSE, AND OTHER

- Typing 70 wpm; accurate 10 key
- Expert in Word, Word Perfect, Excel, Outlook, ProLaw, Elite, Desksite, INSZoom, and ERA accounting software
- Excellent written and verbal communication
- Extremely organized, detail oriented; fast learner
- Notary, commission expires 2014
- Member of Diversity Subcommittee at Tonkon Torp LLP
- Captain of Race for the Cure at Tonkon Torp LLP team two years in a row

EDUCATION

Attended Portland Community College, 2002 - 2006, Psychology and Criminology

REFERENCES

Personal and professional references gladly given upon request.